Jhal
a very good morning friend this is vagina
kasana n r rao question so kuch ho bhaiya come back
with a very interesting a question of all
of you in which you can participate
and win more exciting prizes fen today
we are going to start this drop question
is so you go home today's question is
our see shuttle I give for you guys
after day work you in law and
evening person days you reached home mage
taxi driving license you don't go home
and don't know you guys can answer this
now by going to the link
which is given in the description below you
can answer it by giving the correct answer
you can win many exciting prizes
and on daily basis you
mean every day we Store Play will
share with you five question spots throughout the day in each of the
two parts in which you can
participate you can answer that only once
in one question  You
can participate but you can participate and all 5
questions, in which
after 2 hours you can go outside and a new
question will be displayed
and you can participate in it
and you can make your friends and your
family members participate among themselves
and the safety and gas which is
Shetty's judicial mix and the safety
equipments, you can win them at
different prices and I
would like to tell you that by which you
participate in it and you win and the
result of this is Brinjals, we will announce
in our show where our Yash
comes at 10:00 pm in Plant Speaking, in that we
will announce your pimples that
that valve year we biscuits and
you can also go to our channel on YouTube and
you can watch it on Facebook, right now
we will display the Neem without any side,
regarding the best and from
there you can know who is winning, this is how it
happens  When there are questions sometimes there are
possibilities that more than one
entry comes in the Twinkle lottery
system in which we will decide
who will win. You can come on daily basis,
join us and
participate in our competition and you
can win exciting prizes. This is a search
which is our main motif of India Gate Road
Price. You must have come to know
that we are participating in 10 to make people aware regarding road
safety. So today
our theme is Headquarters Road Safety, on which
we will talk, our questions are
related to
Srishti. Now you
can participate further in it and tell us how can you be a
part of 10 and now you can
win exciting prizes in it and we
Raphael means if we talk about everyday means
road safety safety rules, what we understand from Srishti is that how one can we
save and everyday likes everyday search the self
birds pages, follow that.  Road safety is
important for those who are using it. It is
very important to
understand that the road safety rules that we have
made for road safety are for us and
not for anyone else. It is very important
that we follow those rules not for
ourselves but for others.
We always say that whatever is important in this regard is
for us because if
we do not commit any mistake, it can create a problem for others and can
harm others. So,
we will have to be responsible not only for ourselves but for others as well. If
we become responsible, then somewhere or the other we
can make our daily life happier and
because of them, if we go out sometimes, we come to know
that as we go on the road,
we see that people are
walking keeping a certain distance between themselves. There are
special shoes for them, like potatoes, they
stop the vehicles before the crossing.  They
give you a
gate more to go, why don't you mean not just
for others, if there is
a traffic policeman in front of you,
we will first show him, there are cameras
installed, so for this reason,
not for that thing, we should participate
in this thing to make our day better,
we should
think to ourselves that if we
become responsible, then we can make our day better, and
if we talk about seat belts or
wearing helmets, when we are
going in cars, then we should wear seat belts not only
for others but for ourselves because
we can save people somewhere or the other, we can
save ourselves if any major
accident happens because when we
travel, now we mean every day, but we do
not know when what can happen, so for
your safety, if you wear it, which
we wear every day, then when we travel,
road safety is not for everyone, which is not for us
because your body is safe, it is
also for your family members,
not for yourself, for your family, for your family, for
your parents, for your boss
Meaning, for those people, you should take care of your safety
because your value for them is
probably somewhere
much more than you, so for us,
road safety is mainly not for ourselves but for our
family members who are connected to us
and once for them, we should follow road safety and the
missions and so that
you have seen that we have just come back with a
very interesting show play, but luck
tips, so believe me, you can also join
part of the, now we can add our friends with us, you
can also add our members and by
coming on a daily basis, you
can win many exciting prizes, so as you
can see, this question is displayed on my screen,
which is our
skin question for today, so I will repeat that once
for all that you and then
work in royal and evening with chopped
days, you reached home maize, that is a gotra and
this dandruff, Kapil Dev enjoyed the party in the evening, he had
Android  You have done it and now you have to go
back home so we welcome back
dating taxi taxi driving will
drive you to their home
you won't go back home you will stay there
and don't know you don't know so
come join us and you
can participate
in the candy crush show and increase exciting
prizes so there is Delhi Vis we
go and then there are a lot of officers who make the
common people follow that for
tourist pressure - we go and do it together
with friends and there are a
lot of them that we have
our post office so what
can we do mobile by coming run you can
either we can do our own we mean we can do a seal
or people can also type
them on their own if they are limited for school
if they are a little Peter then Gaurav or you
can stay with your friends or there are a
lot of options it
depends on you what you choose to
avoid accidents because if you are
brown then you are just from somewhere
Not destruction, but harm, you
can also harm someone else who may
not be at fault, so he understood, answer, you can
become a part of this campaign, you can become a part of road safety,
you
can change people's lives because somewhere
we say that when we change, then
perhaps one step of ours can make people's lives better across the country
because instead of
picking on others, if we
change ourselves, then somewhere we can
change things to a great extent. We talk about
road safety and the road safety
rules, if we talk about
YouTube videos which people keep watching
but will follow them, we
see them in many remote areas, when we move away from the city, there are
many
cord men in the cities, if we go around
and in small
cities, when we cross the road, the
people there
avoid helmets etc. They are not thinking police, so
we need to make
some changes in our mindset.  There is a
need somewhere that the helmets we wear are
not for others, we are using them for ourselves
and it is for our safety
because if by chance some problem occurs
then it can harm us somewhere, it can be
very dangerous for you, you can become
paralyzed or you
can even lose your life, so not for others,
we should wear these helmets for ourselves, for the happiness of our loved ones,
we should
use safety measures, there is a
photo that
you can see, Om you should come and put as much
pressure as possible,
come and participate in this school and make people
aware that how we can spread Rok Shetty and make
people understand
one by one and you
can instil your family and friends in this show,
from here and here in the description there will be a link,
you can go to that and give your answers, this question will be
common only for 2 hours, after that
our other members will come and
share their next question with you,
you can participate in that
You are also in that, it means there is
no such training that if you participate in it
then you cannot participate in the next one
but this is part of all the
five questions and it is possible that you may get a
chance to pass more than one so as you can
see on your screen and the
question which is after day's work you enjoy GD evening
person dinner you reach home me then
now cash withdrawal can be done in yes
you don't go home and don't no so you can
use a part of it and you can
win a lot of exciting
prizes
some 10 points to eyes only so come quickly and
participate and GTA is a very
exciting game on
jhal jhal
jhal
some dreams that how many sample questions is there
inquiry can answer bandit rough as many
people as possible come join in this and you
can get a lot of exciting gifts
through typing your fans can bring part of
the and illegally related that which is
every 2 hours  Whatever we have will come
with every new question, subscribe
now, whatever question is there in every question,
you can leave it on our YouTube channel, you can
answer it and you
can win, so it means come and in which you can win
from Jhalawar, for today Chanakya,
thank you and our new, you are still up to date
with new questions.